A Guide to the Joseph H. Willits Papers FA054
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Excellence and Mediocrity in Colleges and Universities", 1950-1969, bulk 1960-1969; 1960-1969; 4
  - Source File - Notes and Clippings, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 31, Folder 214)
  - Source File - Notes and Clippings, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 31, Folder 215)
  - Source File - Speeches and Reprints (A-C) (Box 31, Folder 216)
  - Source File - Speeches and Reprints (D-H) (Box 31, Folder 217)
  - Source File - Speeches and Reprints (Kerr, Clark), 1963 (Box 31, Folder 218)
  - Source File - Speeches and Reprints (K-Z) (Box 32, Folder 219)
  - Interviews (A-H), 1961-1963 (Box 32, Folder 220)
  - Interviews (I-Z), 1961-1963 (Box 32, Folder 221)
  - Nora Beeson - Book Reviews (A-C), circa 1962 (Box 32, Folder 222)
  - Nora Beeson - Book Reviews (D-M), circa 1962 (Box 32, Folder 223)
  - Nora Beeson - Book Reviews (N-Z), circa 1962 (Box 32, Folder 224)
  - Nora Beeson - Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 32, Folder 225)
  - Nora Beeson - Notes and Outlines, 1961-1963; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 226)
  - Nora Beeson - Notes and Outlines, 1961-1963; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 227)
  - Nora Beeson - Notes and Outlines, 1961-1963; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 228)
- Armonk and Byram Hills Schools, 1937-1964, bulk 1960-1964; 1960-1964; 5
  This series consists of two sets of alphabetical files relating to Dr. Willits's service on the Boards of Education for the Westchester County community of Armonk. In June 1961, the Armonk, Middle Patent, and Bear Ridge School Districts consolidated to form the Byram Hills Central School District.
  - Armonk Schools - American Association of School Administrators (AASA), 1962 (Box 33, Folder 229)
  - Armonk Schools - Alexander, Mary (Mrs. John), 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 230)
  - Armonk Schools - Allen, James E., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 231)
  - Armonk Schools - Annual Reports for School District #5, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 232)
  - Armonk Schools - Armonk Teachers' Association (ATA), 1962 (Box 33, Folder 233)
  - Armonk Schools - Applications - District Principal Opening, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 234)
  - Armonk Schools - Audio-Visual, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 235)
  - Armonk Schools - Baldwin, New York Public Schools, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 236)
  - Armonk Schools - Benton, Chauncey F., 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 237)
  - Armonk Schools - Bids, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 238)
  - Armonk Schools - Board of Education Meetings, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 239)
  - Armonk Schools - Board of Cooperative Education Services (BOCES), 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 240)
  - Armonk Schools - Bryan, Bernard L., 1960 (Box 34, Folder 241)
  - Armonk Schools - Bucher, Charles (Merit Pay), 1962 (Box 34, Folder 242)
  - Armonk Schools - Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 243)
  - Armonk Schools - Buildings and Grounds Application Forms, undated (Box 34, Folder 244)
  - Armonk Schools - Business Management News, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 245)
  - Armonk Schools - Carpenter, John, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 246)
  - Armonk Schools - Centralization, 1959-1961 (Box 34, Folder 247)
  - Armonk Schools - Centralization Information, 1952, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 248)
  - Armonk Schools - Civil Defense Policy, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 249)
  - Armonk Schools - Conferences, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 250)
  - Armonk Schools - Crittenden, Harold C., 1960-1962 (Box 34, Folder 251)
  - Armonk Schools - Curriculum, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 252)
  - Armonk Schools - Data Processing, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 253)
  - Armonk Schools - Duties of Personnel, undated (Box 34, Folder 254)
  - Armonk Schools - Education Program - In-Service, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 255)
  - Armonk Schools - Faculty Information, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 256)
  - Armonk Schools - Federal Aid, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 257)
  - Armonk Schools - Gifted, The, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 258)
  - Armonk Schools - Harvard Graduate School of Education - Pamphlets, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 259)
  - Armonk Schools - Hess, Fritz, 1961-1963 (Box 35, Folder 260)
  - Armonk Schools - Hill, Louis, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 261)
  - Armonk Schools - Johnstown, New York Schools, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 262)
  - Armonk Schools - Leave of Absence, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 263)
  - Armonk Schools - Legal Interpretations, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 264)
  - Armonk Schools - Legislative Program, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 265)
  - Armonk Schools - Library, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 266)
  - Armonk Schools - Livingstone, Mary, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 267)
  - Armonk Schools - Manual - Board of Education, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 268)
  - Armonk Schools - Medical Insurance, undated (Box 35, Folder 269)
  - Armonk Schools - Merit Pay, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 270)
  - Armonk Schools - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 271)
  - Armonk Schools - Music, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 272)
  - Armonk Schools - Nurse, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 273)
  - Armonk Schools - Physicians, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 274)
  - Armonk Schools - Pound, Charles, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 275)
  - Armonk Schools - Recreation, 1959-1962 (Box 35, Folder 276)
  - Armonk Schools - Recruitment, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 277)
  - Armonk Schools - Retirement, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 278)
  - Armonk Schools - Salary Schedules, 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 279)
  - Armonk Schools - Salary Survey, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 280)
  - Armonk Schools - School Calendar, 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 281)
  - Armonk Schools - School District Reorganization - New York State Government Documents, 1958-1961 (Box 36, Folder 282)
  - Armonk Schools - School District Reorganization - U. S. Government Documents, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 283)
  - Armonk Schools - Speech to Teachers, March 12, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 284)
  - Armonk Schools - Survey Report, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 285)
  - Armonk Schools - Tax Rates, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 286)
  - Armonk Schools - Teacher Application Forms, undated (Box 36, Folder 287)
  - Armonk Schools - Teacher Recruitment, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 288)
  - Armonk Schools - Tenure, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 289)
  - Armonk Schools - Transportation, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 290)
  - Armonk Schools - Treasurer's Report, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 291)
  - Armonk Schools - Warren, F. B., 1962 (Box 37, Folder 292)
  - Armonk Schools - Westchester Teachers' Association, 1959-1962 (Box 37, Folder 293)
  - Byram Hills Schools - David, John B., 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 294)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Educational Conference Report, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 295)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Elzay, Jack, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 296)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Grove, Richard N., 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 297)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Howe, Harold, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 298)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Kesselheim, A. Donn, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 299)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Lloyd, Francis, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 300)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Michael, Lloyd S., 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 301)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Policy Manual, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 302)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Report - "Planning for the Future", 1962 (Box 37, Folder 303)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Wheaton, Gordon A., 1962 (Box 37, Folder 304)
  - Byram Hills Schools - Woodring, Paul, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 305)
- Joseph H. Willits photographs, 1944-1955; 1039
  Photographs
  - Joseph H. Willits, 1944-1955 (Box 15, Folder 196)